Hafiz Elfia Wedo Putra

hafizelfiawedoputra@outlook.com | linkedin.com/in/hafizewp | github.com/hafizewp22

SUMMARY

I have 1+ year's experience in web developer at my internship company and am interested in technology. I am also a hard worker, have integrity, responsibility, and work in a team. Really likes to learn coding such as websites and data analysis to make interesting programs.

EDUCATION

BINA NUSANTARA UNIVERSITY

Jakarta, Indonesia

Bachelor of Computing in Computer Science

2019 - Present

Streaming: Database Technology

GPA: 3.23 / 4.0

VOCATIONAL HIGH SCHOOL OF INFORMATICS SERANG

Serang, Indonesia

Software Engineering

2016 – 2019

Point: 81 / 100

EXPERIENCE

PT. TELKOM INDONESIA

Jakarta, Indonesia March 2022 – Present

Web Developer – Internship

- Updating the SIIS (Sales IndiHome Information System) 4.0 website using the ReactJs programming language to update and add features to Maps, website views, and API.
- Participate in training to create a Quiz theme project for the Usecase Bootcamp application..

BINA NUSANTARA UNIVERSITY

Tangerang, Indonesia

Student Mentor

October 2021 – February 2022

 The Community Care for Friends at BINUS University which provides the task of helping friends who have special attention and high concern for disability issues and special needs on campus.

BINA NUSANTARA COMPUTER CLUB - Tangerang, Indonesia

Organization - Learning and Training Staff (August 2020 – February 2022)

- Establish curriculum and class materials and schedules for classes and teaching.
- Become an event committee in organizations related to Information Technology.
- Create and do attendance for each LnT class.

BINA NUSANTARA COMPUTER CLUB

Tangerang, Indonesia July 2019 – October 2022

Organization - Activist

- MC training and talk.
- Student Leadership and Management Exercises (LKMM).
- Training and learning to create Website design (HTML & CSS).

ADDITIONAL

Hard Skill:

HTML, CSS, PHP, Java, Laravel, ReactJS, Figma (Software), MySQL/SQL, Database Design, Data Analysis

Soft Skill:

Teamwork, Time Management, Leadership

Language:

Fluent in Indonesia, Elementary Proficiency in English

Certifications & Training:

Web Development Path (Node.js), HTML Course (Sololearn), Introduction to HTML5 (University of Michigan), Problem Solving Basic (HackerRank), Java Basic (HackerRank), SQL Basic (HackerRank), Database Design and Programming with SQL (Training - Oracle FGA 2021)

Publications:

Augmented Reality for Human Digestive Anatomy Biology Learning (June 2021) [View]

Honors & Awards:

Student Exchange to Thailand (2018), Winner of Designing UI/UX with Figma Competition (3rd place on campus level), Asia Jakarta - Indonesia National Contest 2020 (Rank 70 out of 700 teams)

Project:

Clothing Store Cashier Application in Web (2018), Data Covid-19 Indonesia in Web (2021), Online Store "BukaWarung" (2022), Online Store "JH Furniture" (2022), Kutanya Quiz for ReactJS (2022)